Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Institute of Visual Art Records, 1962-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee Institute of Visual Arts Records, 1962-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Institute of Visual Arts
UWM Archival Collection 217
Accession 2015-042
Accession 2016-011
24.2 cubic ft. (25 boxes) 69 digital image files (490 MB) plus additions of 7 cubic ft. (7 boxes) and 231 digital files (5.3 GB)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of the Institute for Visual Art (Inova), formerly the UWM Art Museum, including information on holdings, exhibits, and administration. The records include correspondence, planning reports, promotional materials, exhibit details and exhibit catalogues, documenting the development of the art collection and management of the art museums and galleries. Also included are exhibition files, which provide details on a wide range of works from emerging student talent, to established local artists, to prominent international exhibits.
The UW-Milwaukee Art Museum was "established to house and administer the art collections of the University and the exhibition programs in the Fine Arts Galleries, in the Art History Galleries, and in the Museum Galleries in Vogel Hall." All of the art collections on campus were to be moved to a renovated Vogel Hall that would become the University Art Museum. However, due to budget constraints in 1980-1981, only a portion of Vogel Hall became available for housing some of the art collections. At this time, the deans of the School of Fine Arts and College of Letters & Sciences agreed that the UWM Art Museum would become a separate entity that would administer all of UWM's art collections, but not necessarily house everything in the same location. The museum opened to the public in 1983.
In 1996, the name of the University Art Museum was changed to the Institute for Visual Arts or Inova. The mission of the new institute remained the same. In 2007, the Institute for Visual Arts relocated to UWM's Kenilworth Building. The institute remained at the Kenilworth building until Fall 2016, when the Peck School of the Arts discontinued support.
Directors of Constituent Galleries
Directors of Fine Arts Galleries
1975-1977 Fred Parker
1977-1983 John L. Taylor
Directors of Art History Galleries
1975-1978 Norman D. Ziff
1978-1979 Alex Seltzer
1979-1983 Mark Chepp
Directors of the UWM Art Museum
1983-1986 Suzanne Foley
1986-1987 Robert Hickok (Acting)
1987-1989 Kent Anderson (Acting)
1989-1997 E. Michael Flanagan
Directors of the Institute for Visual Art
1997-2003 Peter Doroshenko
2005-2012 Bruce Knackert (Acting)
2012-2015 Sara Krajewski
2016 Monica Miller (Gallery Assistant)
The collection contains the records of the Institute for Visual Arts (Inova), formerly the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee (UWM) Art Museum. The institute is tasked with administering, collecting, and exhibiting UWM's art museum in several campus galleries. More detailed scope and content notes are provided at the series level in the content list.
The records of the UW-Milwaukee Institute for Visual Arts are arranged in the following two series. More detailed arrangement notes are provided at the series level in the contents list.
Exhibition Files, 1964-2001
Administrative Files, 1962-2003
The collection contains two additional accessions:
Accession 2015-042: Exhibition Files, 1979-2015
Accession 2016-011: Subject and Exhibition Files, 1991-2016
A spreadsheet with file-level information on the electronic records is available in the Archives department. The spreadsheet contains information on original file name, file size, date of modification of original file, original image size, and file format. Additional technical metadata is available; consult an archivist for more information.
A detailed finding aid for accession 2015-042 is available in the Archives.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
UWM Art Museum Publications UWM Archival Collection 144
UW-Milwaukee School of Fine Arts UWM Archival Collection 81
UW-Milwaukee Institute of Visual Arts Accession Files UWM Archival Collection 209
Administrative/Restriction Information
Electronic files must be viewed on computers in the Archives using the access copies. Contact an archivist for more information.
The file in box 25 is permanently restricted. Contact an archivist for more information.
There are no access restrictions on the remaining materials, and the collection is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
The Institute of Visual Arts transferred the first accession in February 2008 (accession 2007-042) and the second accession in April 2008 (accession 2007-051).
Accession 2015-042 was received from the Peck School of Arts' Dean's Office and separated from Accession 2015-041 in May 2016. Accession 2016-011 was transferred to the Archives in August 2016.
As of November 29, 2016, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core i5-4570 CPU (3.20 GHz, 4 GB RAM) running Windows 7 Enterprise, with Service Pack 1. Software used to access the files includes Windows Picture and Fax Viewer, Windows Media Player, and Notepad.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Tagged Image File Format [.tif]
JPEG File Interchange Format [.jpg]
ASCII Text Document [.txt]
Video Object File [.vob]
Access copies for TIFFs were created by Pixillion Image Converter as JPEG File Interchange Format [.jpg] and were viewable in Windows Picture and Fax Viewer in the same software environment as of June 7, 2013.
Contents List
- Records, 1962-2003
  - 1. Exhibitions, 1964-2001
    This series comprises most of the collection. The records include exhibit planning documents, promotional material, artist correspondence, photographs, slides, and various other documents detailing when, where, and how exhibits were set up. These records also include loan forms and often describe works of art on display. Some exhibits files also include a copy of the catalogue produced.
    Exhibits were frequently changed, allowing for dozens of exhibitions per year. Reoccurring student and faculty exhibits were created to display talented campus artists and in order to satisfy some degree requirements. Other events, such as College for Kids, are part of a university-wide community outreach effort to engage local schoolchildren.
    The series is arranged chronologically. Folders were named based on the exhibition, which described the main artist, the main theme, or both. Exhibits would frequently change, so it is not unusual to find similar promotional material available in neighboring folders, as flyers might promote several upcoming exhibitions at once.
    - Michelangelo Symposium, Budget, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Fine Arts Gallery, Miscellaneous Exhibits, 1964-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Rubbings of Pre-Colombian Sculpture Exhibition, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Priebe, Karl Exhibition, Collection of Paintings and Drawings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Greek Icon Exhibition, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Maas, Paul, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Markowski, Eugene Exhibition, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Lester, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Art History Gallery, Miscellaneous Exhibits, 1967-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Irish Architectural Drawing Exhibit, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Richmond Brown Baker Exhibition, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Thimme Exhibition, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Spector Exhibition, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Stern, Lucia, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Marine Exhibition, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Zocchi, Giussepe, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Skyscrapers Exhibits, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Lipton, Seymour, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Van der Marck, Jan, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Motherwell, Robert, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - German Expressionist Watercolor Exhibit, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Modern Polish Architecture, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Bob Jones Exhibition (Dutch and Flemish Paintings), 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Lachnaise, Gaston, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Soleri, Paolo Exhibit, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Winston Exhibition, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Watteau, Jean-Antoine, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - D'Arcangelo, Allan, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Conservation Exhibit, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Chinese Painting Exhibit, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Levine, Jack, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Royal Building Exhibition, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Yeats, Jack, 1971-1978 (Box 1, Folder 37-38)
    - McGarrell, James, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Siege of Gibraltar Exhibition, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Small Objects, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Kline Drawings, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Armenian Manuscripts, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Segal, George Exhibition, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 44-48)
    - The American Federation of Arts, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Mannerism to Neo-Classicism Exhibit, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Exhibitions, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 20th Century Prints and Drawings Exhibit, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Small Scale Abstract Expressionist Paintings, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Weaver, John C. Exhibit, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Vulpas, George, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Gorky, Arshile, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Quidor, John Exhibition, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
    - Low-Life in the Lowlands, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
    - Armenian Manuscripts, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
    - After Milton Exhibition, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Beckett, Samuel, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Frackelton, Susan, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Antique Art, Milwaukee Art Center, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Ancient Art, Milwaukee Public Museum, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 4x4, Student Exhibit, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Advanced Drawing, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Comic Art, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Lubalin, Herb Design By, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Lutz, Frank Sculpture, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Exhibit, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Directions: Midwest Printmaking, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Bouguereau, William Adolphe, Appraisal, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - French Women, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Madison Street Art, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 19th Century Russian Paintings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 19th Century American Paintings at Bowdoin College, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Comic Art Exhibit, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Children of Milwaukee County, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Space, Form and Materials, Professor Lactman, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Constable, John Symposium and Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
    - Women of Photography, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Dream Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - The Photographic Image, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Burkert, Bob, Student Exhibit, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Middaugh, Bob, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Bresnanan, Dan, Student Exhibit, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Rahr-West Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - New York Artists, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Townley, Hugh, Sculpture, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Visual Communications and Professional Design, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Little, Ken, Ceramics, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Graphics 76: Britain, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Carrel, Dan: Documentation, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Kingsbury-Evans, Ceramics, Student Exhibit, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Chagall, Marc, Dead Souls Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - The Art of the Piranesi, Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - British Prints Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Rosenberg Collection Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Daumier and His Contemporaries Exhibition, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Gelpi, Rene, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Robert Von Neumann Memorial Exhibit, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Arakawa Exhibition, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Rubens Exhibition, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
    - Old Master Drawings for the Ziff Collection, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Gilbert Collection, Photography, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Goundie, George and Friebert, Joseph, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11-13)
    - Arakawa, Graphics Exhibition, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Focus on the Rosenberg Collection, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Asian Art from Milwaukee Collections, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16-24)
    - Faculty Exhibit Loan Forms, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Student Shows, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
    - Gilbert Exhibition, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Wisconsin Watercolor Society Silver Anniversary Exhibition, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 31-32)
    - Film Orders, Background Information, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - The National Invitational Color-Blend Print Exhibit, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - German Expressionism from Milwaukee Collections, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 35-47)
    - The Divine Presence, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 48-66)
    - Schroedter Exhibit, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Russian Stage Design, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Ukiyo-e Woodcuts Exhibition, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - American Graphics of the 1930s, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - African Art, Power and Symbol, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
    - Pinata: Disposable Art and Craft Exhibition, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chambi, Martin, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Asian Art, Religion and Culture And Divine Presence
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Exhibition Files, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 10-14)
    - Fotografia Polska Exhibition, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Lerner, Leslie, Proposal, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Exhibition, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Art of Russia, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Outright 80s: Foreshadowing North American Crafts, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Student Shows, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Emmons C. and King. K, Installation Show, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Student Shows, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
    - Cover Show, American Institute of Graphic Arts, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Gilbert Gallery, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Director's Choice Exhibition, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Beuys, Joseph, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Alice Adam Ltd, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Associated American Artists, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Andre Emmerich, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Brooke Alexander Inc., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Castelli Graphics, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Construct, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Feldman, Ronald, Fine Arts Inc., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Droll/Kolbert, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Director's Choice, Delivery Contracts and Loan Agreements
      - Frumkin and Struve Gallery, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - BC Holland Inc., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Landfall Press Inc., 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Marlborough Gallery, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Parasol Press, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Peterburg Press, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - The Artist Bob Stanley, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Young-Hoffman, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Completed, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Hodgson, Carole Exhibition, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47-49)
    - Cut on Wood Exhibition, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Oyen Collection, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Printmakers and Painters Exhibition, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Hoffman, Hans Exhibit, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Treib, Marc: Recent Posters, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - 1960s Light Sculpture, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Nigerian Textiles Exhibition, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Wisconsin Painters and Sculptors, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 57-70)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 71-73)
    - Phases Exhibition, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Know What You See Exhibit, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Six Senior Painters, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - New York School Paintings, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 77-84)
    - Vilmouth, Jean-Luc Exhibition, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Face to Face Exhibition, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - African Roots of Haitian Art, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Art of American Fashion Exhibition, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Mande Ideology in Art Exhibition, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4-10)
    - Sinclair, Gerrit, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11-16)
    - "Reflections on the Milwaukee Journal Gallery of Wisconsin Art" Show, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Daumier and Gavarni, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 19-22)
    - Student Exhibition, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Show, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
    - Late Gothic Sculpture from Northern Europe, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Vigango: The Commemorative Sculpture of Kenya, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Expressions in Bronze Exhibition, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - The Gift of Reverend Josephus Farmer Exhibition, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 29-35)
    - Motherwell, Robert: Lyric Suite Exhibition, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Selections from the Joseph and Ilma Uihlein Bequest, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Student Juried Exhibition, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Lenders' Copies of Loan Forms, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Drawings: Art Faculty of UW System, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 40-55)
    - Wisconsin Painters and Sculptors, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 56-62)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Faculty Exhibition, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Roberta, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Racine, Rober Exhibit, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - University Art Museum Opening, Event Arrangements, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6-10)
    - Bornstein, Eli Exhibition, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 11-13)
    - Passion and Prophecy: The Art of Jennings Tofel Exhibition, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin Art Education Association, Teachers Exhibition, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
    - Faculty Exhibition, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17-19)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
    - Ancient Art from Milwaukee Collections, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 22-24)
    - 5 Suites of Prints, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - The Rogers Collection, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Twenty-Five Years of Discovery at Sardis, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Layton School of Art Legacy Exhibition, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Student Show, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Baroque Art in Italy, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 30-36)
    - Public Relations, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Melanesian Art: Dialogue with the Spirits, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 38-43)
    - Tourism Information, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Naturalism and Metaphor Exhibition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 45-47)
    - Art of the Comic Book, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
    - Student Exhibition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Print Exhibition, Michal and Shawn, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Pierce, Danny Exhibition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
    - Collections '85, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Paintings from Spain's American Dominions: Ecuador and Peru, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Faculty/Student Drawing Exhibition, Fall, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3-6)
    - Color Photography: New Work, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Celebration 100: A Century of Alumni Art, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8-19)
    - Adornments, Exhibition, Catalogue, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
    - Vincent Canacle: Pastel Still Lifes Exhibition, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Pandora to Mother Goose: Images of Women in Mid-Eighteeth to Early Nineteenth Century English Prints, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23-25)
    - Schroedter, Howard, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 26-28)
    - World War I Posters from the Roberts S. Zigman Collection, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Face and Heart: The Figure in Mesoamerican Sculpture Exhibition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - The Architecture of Yesteryear: Presentation Drawings of Milwaukee Architects, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 33-35)
    - Student Exhibition, Ceramics, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Faculty Exhibition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 37-38)
    - Print Show, Working Papers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Postmodernism: A Spectacle of Reflexivity, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Henri Matisse: Lithographs and Bronzes from the Cone Collection, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 41-42)
    - Reactions to the War: European Art, 1914-1925, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Eichenberg, Fritz Exhibition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Art from Nomad and Village Looms, Exhibition, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 45-47)
    - Scarborough/Dusseldorf, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 48-55)
    - Student Exhibition, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - UWM Alumni Association Exhibition, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 57-58)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Fine Arts Gallery, Permanent Collection Exhibition, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Wisconsin Painters and Sculptors, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Napoleon To Egypt: Images from the Description De L'Egypte Exhibition, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Postmodernism in Contemporary Art, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Student Exhibition, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 65-67)
    - Grunwald Collection, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Art of an Emergent Nation: American Painting from 1775-1865, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - American Painting: 1750-1865, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Wit and Vitriol: Hogarth and the Politics of His Time Exhibition, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 6-11)
    - Edward Steichen/109 Exhibition, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 12-18)
    - Realisms Exhibit, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 19-30)
    - The Art of Design Exhibition, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 31-32)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 33-34)
    - Student Exhibit, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Faculty Exhibition, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Navajo Blankets, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Exhibitions, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Seymour Rosofsky and the Chicago Imagist Tradtion Exhibition, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
    - Leenhouts, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
    - Student Exhibition, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7-13)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Max Arthur Conn: Art in the 1930s, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Robert Van Neumann: Works on Paper, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 16-20)
    - January Exhibit Openings, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Prints and Multiples from the Experimental Workshop Exhibition, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 22-25)
    - African Art from the Richard Hunt Collection, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - 20th Century Small Scale Sculpture from the Rosenburg Collection, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Marc Chagall "Dead Souls" Exhibit, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - L'Heritage Visuel de France, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
    - Clarice Logan Memorial Exhibit, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Contemporary Masters, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Townley, Hugh, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
    - The Holy Ranger: Martin Jack Rosenblum Exhibition, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Ethnographic Art from Faculty Collections, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)